Streib, Victor; Papers apap330
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Case Files, 1947-2012, Undated; 1; 19 cubic ft.
  - Executed Juveniles, United States, 1982-2007, Undated; 1.3; 4 cubic ft.
    - Washington: Walter Dubue, executed 1931-07-11, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 53)
    - Washington: Joseph Nuana, executed 1874-03-06, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 54)
    - Washington: William White, executed 1905-03-17, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 55)
    - Washington: Sim Johnson, executed 1891-06-19, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 56)
    - Washington: Laban Walker, executed 1879-11-28, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 57)
    - West Virginia: Charles Miller, executed 1892-04-22, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 58)
    - West Virginia: Geow Yee, executed 1921-03-11, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 59)
  - Sentenced Juveniles, United States, 1978-2007, Undated; 1.4; 6.9 cubic ft.
    - Executed Juveniles: general, 1984; 2001; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Alabama: Renaldo Adams, sentenced 1998-12-11, 2001; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Alabama: Michael Barnes, sentenced 1995, 2003; 2004; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Alabama: James Bonds, sentenced 2002-11-11 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Alabama: Roy Burgess, Jr. 1994-12-09, 1992; 2001; 2004; 2006 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Alabama: Taurus Carroll, sentenced 1998-02-13, 2001; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Alabama: Timothy Davis, sentenced 1980-07-28, 1986; 1999; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Alabama: Mark Anthony Duke, sentenced 1999-03-24, 2001; 2005; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - Alabama: Trace Duncan, sentenced 1996-03-09, 2001; 2005; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - Alabama: Calyton Joel Flowers, sentenced 1990-02-23, 1991; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - Alabama: Jeffrey Franklin, sentenced 1998-03-10 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - Alabama: Gary Hart Davis II, sentenced 1998-03-10, 2001; 2005; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - Alabama: James Hyde, sentenced 1996-07-19, 1998; 2001; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - Alabama: Carnel Jackson, sentenced 1981-11-20, 1986; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - Alabama: William Knotts, sentenced 1992-08-01, 2001; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - Alabama: Kenney Loggins, sentenced 1996-03-09, 2001; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - Alabama: Frederick Lynn, sentenced 1983-05-31, 1990; 1992; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - Alabama: Marcus Pressley, sentenced 1997-10-10, 2001; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - Alabama: Nathan Slaton, sentenced 1990-05-22, 2001; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - Alabama: Shaber Wimberly, sentenced 1998-07-30, 2001; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - Alabama: Gregory Wynn, sentenced 1999-09-17, 2001 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)
    - Arizona: Tonatihu Aguilar, sentenced 2001-10-26, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - Arizona: Jonathan Doody, sentenced 1993-07-13, 2007; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - Arizona: James Edward Davolt, II, sentenced 2000, 2001; 2004; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 24)
    - Arizona: Raul Martin Fong, sentenced 1994-02-04, 1999; 2004; 2005; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 25)
    - Arizona: Christopher "Bo" Huerstel, sentenced 2001-03-23, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 26)
    - Arizona: Levi Jackson, sentenced 1994-01-26, 1997; 2001; 2004; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 27)
    - Arizona: Jesus Jimenez, sentenced 1988-01-22, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 28)
    - Arizona: Ken Laird, sentenced 1994-04-15, 1999; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 29)
    - Arizona: Frank James Valencia, sentenced 1979, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 30)
    - Arkansas: Damond Sanford, sentenced 1996-01-19 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 31)
    - Arkansas: Ronald Ward, sentenced 1985-09-20, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 32)
    - Delaware: Linwood Shields, sentenced 1975, 2003; 2007; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 33)
    - Florida: general, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 34)
    - Florida: Jerome Allen, Motion to Strike death penalty and order denying, 1991 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 35)
    - Florida: Jerome Allen, Judgement: trial court, 1991 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 36)
    - Florida: Jerome Allen, initial brief, 1991 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 37)
    - Florida: Jerome Allen, Answer Brief, 1991 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 38)
    - Florida: Amici Children First, 1991 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 39)
    - Florida: Jerome Allen Amici Pub Def., 1991 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 40)
    - Florida: Jerome Allen, 1991 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 41)
    - Florida: Jerome Allen, 1991; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 42)
    - Florida: Jerome Allen, 1992 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 43)
    - Florida: Jerome Allen, 2002; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Florida: Jerome Allen, sentenced 1991, 1995; 1998; 2001 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Florida: Ronald Lee Bell, Jr., sentenced 2000-05-16, 2002; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Florida: James Bonifay, sentenced 1991-09-20, 1997; 2003; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Florida: Keith Brennan, sentenced 1997-03-20, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Florida: Henry Brown, sentenced 1975-08, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Florida: Memwaldy Curtis, sentenced 1984-07-28, 1997; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Florida: Ralph Ellis, sentenced 1989, 1993; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - Florida: Jeffery Farina, sentenced 1992-12-16, 1994; 2002; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - Florida: Roderick Ferrell, sentenced 1998-02-27, 2001; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - Florida: Bernell Hegwood, sentenced 1988-03-29, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - Florida: Wilburn Lamb, sentenced 1989-05-10, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - Florida: Cleo Douglas Lecroy, sentenced 1986-10-01, 2003; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - Florida: Jesse James Livingston, sentenced 1985-10-23, 1986; 2003; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - Florida: Paul Edward Magill, sentenced 1977-04-25, 1985; 1984; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - Florida: Paul Magill, sentenced 1977-04-25, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - Florida: Randall Moe, sentenced 1982-01, 1992; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - Florida: James Morgan, sentenced 1977-12-30, 1992; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - Florida: James Morgan, sentenced 1977-12-30, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - Florida: Robert Peavy, sentenced 1982-05, 1992; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - Florida: Nathan Ramirez, 1996, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)
    - Florida: Frank Ross, sentenced 1977-10-23, 1991; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - Florida: Rossiny st. Clair, sentenced 2001-12-17, 2002 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - Florida: Willie Simpson, sentenced 1976-05, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 24)
    - Florida: David Snipes, sentenced 1997-04-11, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 25)
    - Florida: Larry Thompson, sentenced 1974-01, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 26)
    - Florida: Ryan Urban, sentenced 1996, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 27)
    - Florida: George Vasil, sentenced 1974-12, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 28)
    - Georgia: General, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 29)
    - Georgia: Clinton Branston, sentenced 1980s, 1994 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 30)
    - Georgia: Janice Buttrum, sentenced 1981-03-31, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 31)
    - Georgia: Exzavious Gibson, sentenced 1990-02-02, 2002; 2004 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 32)
    - Georgia: Samuel Gibson, sentenced 1975, 2002; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 33)
    - Georgia: Gary Lee Hawes, sentenced 1975, 1991; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 34)
    - Georgia: Larry Jenkins, sentenced 1995-09, 2000; 2002 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 35)
    - Georgia: Andrew Legare, sentenced 1977-11-23, 1986; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 36)
    - Georgia: Alexander Williams, sentenced 1986-08-29, 1994; 2000; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 37)
    - Indiana: Gregory Dickens, sentenced 1999-05, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 38)
    - Indiana: Keith Patton, sentenced 1984, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 39)
    - Indiana: Jay Thompson, sentenced 1982-03-18, 1986; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 40)
    - Kentucky: Todd Ice, sentenced 1980-10-09, 1986; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 41)
    - Kentucky: Larry Osborne, sentenced 1984-11-29, 2001; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 42)
    - Kentucky: Kevin Stanford, Correspondence, 2005 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 43)
    - Kentucky: Kevin Stanford case files, 1983 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Kentucky: Kevin Stanford: Latent Fingerprint Report, 1981 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Kentucky: Kevin Stanford, transcript of 8-31-81 hearing, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Kentucky: Kevin Stanford, background reports, 2002; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Kentucky: Kevin Stanford, reply brief, 1988 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Kentucky: Kevin Stanford, writ of certiorari, 1988 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Kentucky: Kevin Stanford, writ of certiorari, 1989 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Kentucky: Kevin Stanford, Inter-American Commission Human Rights, 1999 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - Kentucky: Kevin Stanford, sixth circuit appeal, 2001 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - Kentucky: Kevin Stanford, sixth circuit appeal, 2001 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - Kentucky: Kevin Stanford, ky statute, 2001 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - Kentucky: Kevin Stanford Case files and news, 2001 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - Kentucky: Kevin Stanford, amicus brief, 2002 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - Kentucky: Kevin Stanford, case files & correspondence, 1988; 1996 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - Kentucky: Kevin Stanford, case files & correspondence, 2000 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - Kentucky: Kevin Stanford clemency, 2002 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - Louisiana: Roy Bridgewater, sentenced 1997, 2002; 2005 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - Louisiana: Joseph Brown, sentenced 1981-05-01, 2002; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - Louisiana: Adam Comeaux, sentenced 1986-02-14, 2002; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - Louisiana: Dale Dwayne Craig, sentenced 1994-09-27, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - Louisiana: Shareef Cousin, sentenced 1996-01-30, 1990; 1998; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)
    - Louisiana: Troy Dugar, sentenced 1987-05-01, 1988; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - Louisiana: Cedric D'wayne Howard, sentenced 1999?, 2003 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - Louisiana: Lawrence Jacobs, sentenced 1998-05, 2002; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Louisiana: Joseph Marshall, sentenced 1980-10, 1988; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Louisiana: Ryan Matthews, sentenced 1999-09-02, 2002 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Louisiana: John L. Neal, sentenced 1990-05, 2004 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Louisiana: Johnny Ross, sentenced 1975, 2002; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Louisiana: David Rushing, sentenced 1983-10-04, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Louisiana: Reginald Smith, sentenced 1979, 1987; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Louisiana: Gary Tyler, sentenced 1975, 1989; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - Louisiana: Corey Williams, sentenced 2000, 2001 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - Louisiana: Aaron Wilson, sentenced 2002-08-17 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - Maryland: Lawrence Johnson, sentenced 1982-10-06, 1989; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - Maryland: James Trimble, sentenced 1982-03-19, 1984; 1988; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - Mississippi: general, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - Mississippi: David Blue, sentenced 1993-04-02, 2003 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - Mississippi: Kevin Coleman, sentenced 1979, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - Mississippi: Kevin Dycus, sentenced 1988, 2004 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - Mississippi: Roderick Eskridge, sentenced 1999-01-26, 2002; 2004; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - Mississippi: Ronald Chris Foster, sentenced 1991-01-17, 2002; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - Mississippi: William Holley, sentenced 1993-03-03, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - Mississippi: Larry Jones, sentenced 1975-03-19, 1985; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - Mississippi: Stephen McGilberry, sne. 1996-02-09, 1999; 2001; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)
    - Mississippi: James Mhoon, sentenced 1983-09-16, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - Mississippi: Clanton D. Pickle, sentenced 1975, 1994; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - Mississippi: George Davis Tokman, sentenced 1981-09-10, 1983; 1986; 1988; 1990; 1994 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 24)
    - Mississippi: George David Tokman, sentenced 1981-09-10, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 25)
    - Missouri: Heath Wilkins, sentenced 1986-06-27, 1985; 1988; 1992; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 26)
    - Missouri: Heath Wilkins, sentenced 1986-06-27, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 27)
    - Missouri: Heath Wilkins, sentenced 1986-06-27, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 28)
    - Missouri: Heath Wilkins, sentenced 1986-06-27, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 29)
    - Montana: Antonio Richardson, sentenced 1993-07-02, 1994; 2001; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 30)
    - Montana: Chris Simmons, sentenced 1994-08-19, 2002; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 31)
    - Montana: Chris Simmons, sentenced 1994-08-19, 2002; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Montana: Christopher Simmons, sentenced 1994-08-19, 2004; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Montana: Christopher Simmons, sentenced 1994-08-19, 2002; 2004; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Nebraska: Rodney Stewart, sentenced 1975-08-20, 2002; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Nevada: Michael Domingues, sentenced 1994, 2002; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Nevada: Michael Domingues, sentenced 1994, 1988; 1995; 1991 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Nevada: Frederick Harvey, sentenced 1984, Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Nevada: Robert Servin, sentenced 2000, 2002; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - New Jersey: Marco Bey, sentenced 1983-09-15, 1984; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - North Carolina: Thomas Adams, sentenced 1988-11-19, 1989; 2002; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - North Carolina: Leon Brown, sentenced 1984-10-26, Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - North Carolina: Lamoms Chapman, sentenced 2000-04-11, 2002 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - North Carolina: Kevin Golphin, sentenced 1998-05-14, 2002; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - North Carolina: Richard Joyner, sentenced 1989-05-25, Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - North Carolina: Freddie Lee Stokes, sentenced 1982-06-02, 1985 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - North Carolina: Francisco Tirado, sentenced 2000-04-11, 2002; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - North Carolina: Travis Walters, sentenced 2001-04-05, 2002 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - North Carolina: Curtis Womble, sentenced 1994, Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - Ohio: Carl Lamont Bayless, sentenced 1974, Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - Ohio: William Lee Bell, sentenced 1975, 1991; 1994; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - Ohio: Ronnie Bridgeman, sentenced 1975?, 1991 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)
    - Ohio: Mark Anthony Davis, sentenced 1976, Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - Ohio: John Harris, sentenced 1974-11-08, Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - Ohio: Willie Johnson, sentenced 1975, 1991 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 24)
    - Ohio: Paul Starks, sentenced 1977?, 1991 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 25)
    - Oklahoma: general, Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 26)
    - Oklahoma: John Bootwell, sentenced 1980's, Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 27)
    - Oklahoma: Monty Lee Eddings, sentenced 1978, Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 28)
    - Oklahoma: Monty Lee Eddings, sentenced 1978, 1983; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 29)
    - Oklahoma: Derrick Lester, sentenced 1998, Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 30)
    - Oklahoma: Jerry Dwayne Mooney, sentenced 1993, Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 31)
    - Oklahoma: William Wayne Thompson, sentenced 1984-01-06, 1986; 1996; 2003; 2004; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 32)
    - Oklahoma: William Wayne Thompson, Supreme Court Briefs, 1986 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 33)
    - Oklahoma: William Wayne Thompson Supreme Court Brief, 1986 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 34)
    - Oklahoma: William Wayne Thompson Supreme Court Brief, 1986 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 35)
    - Oklahoma: William Wayne Thompson, Supreme Court Brief, 1986 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Oklahoma: William Wayne Thompson Supreme Court Brief, 1986 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Oklahoma: William Wayne Thompson amicus brief, 1984 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Oklahoma: William Wayne Thompson, amicus brief, 1987; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Oklahoma: William Wayne Thompson, Supreme Court Petition, 1986; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Oklahoma: William Wayne Thompson. Statement of case, 1986; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Oklahoma: William Wayne Thompson, transcript, pt. 1, 1984 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Oklahoma: William Wayne Thompson, transcripts, pt. 2, 1984 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - Oklahoma: William Wayne Thompson, transcripts, pt. 3, 1984 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - Oklahoma: William Wayne Thompson, transcripts pt. 4, 1984 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - Oklahoma: William Wayne Thompson, case files, 1987 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - Oklahoma: William Wayne Thompson, case files, 1985; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - Oklahoma: William Wayne Thompson, Petitioner's brief, Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Pennsylvania: Joseph General Aulisio, sentenced 1984-05-17, 1982; 1986; 1995; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Pennsylvania: John Blount, sentenced 1990-11-09, 1991; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Pennsylvania: Derrick Hawey, sentenced 1999, 2002; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Pennsylvania: Kevin Hughes, sentenced 1981-03, 1986; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Pennsylvania: Percy Lee, 1986, 1989; 2002; 2003; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Pennsylvania: Antonio Ligons, sentenced 1999-06-01, 2002; 2003 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Pennsylvania: Raymond Williams, sentenced 1987-03-18, Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - South Carolina: general, Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - South Carolina: Richard Conyers, sentenced 1994-02-17, 2003; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - South Carolina: Joseph Hudgins, sentenced 1993-07-28, 2000; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - South Carolina: Herman Hughes, sentenced 1995, 1997; 2000; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - South Carolina: William Kelly, sentenced 1989-09-29, 2002; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - South Carolina: Eric Morgan, sentenced 2004-03-09, Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - South Carolina: Ted Benjamin Powers, sentenced 1996-02-29, 2000; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - South Carolina: Rudolph Tyrner, sen, 1978, 2003; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - Tennessee: general, 1985 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - Texas: general 1999, Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - Texas: Robert Acuna, sentenced 2004-08-11, Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - Texas: Steven Alvardo, sentenced 1993-10-05, 1994; 2002; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - Texas: Randy Arroyo, sentenced 1998-03-06, 2003; 2005; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)
    - Texas: Mauro Barraza, sentenced 1991-04-08, 1993; 2002; 2005; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - Texas: Leroy Barrow, sentenced 1982-04-26, Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - Texas: Billy Joe Battle, sentenced 1975?, Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 24)
    - Texas: Johnnie Bernal, sentenced 1995, 2003; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 25)
    - Texas: Victor Burns, sentenced 1981-09-14, 1986; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 26)
    - Texas: Mark Arthur, sentenced 1997-12-17, 2002; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 27)
    - Texas: Edward Capetillo, sentenced 1996-03-28, 2002; 2005; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 28)
    - Texas: Raymond Cobb, sentenced 1999-02-27, 2002; 2004; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 29)
    - Texas: John C. Dewberry, sentenced 1996-11-21, 1998; 2001; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 30)
    - Texas: Justin Wiley Dickens, sentenced 1996-09-18, Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 31)
    - Texas: Anthony Dixon, sentenced 1995, 2004; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 32)
    - Texas: Bernard Ferguson, sentenced 1977, Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 33)
    - Texas: Derek Guillen, sentenced 1999?, 2002; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 34)
    - Texas: Patrick Horn, sentenced 1999-10-04, 2002; 2004 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 35)
    - Texas: Efren C. Ibanez, sentenced 1980, Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 36)
    - Texas: Jimmy Jackson, sentenced 1985, 2005; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 37)
    - Texas: Eddie Johnson, sentenced 1997-07-31, 2002; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 38)
    - Texas: Anzel jones, sentenced 1996-06-04, 2002; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 39)
    - Texas: Troy Albert Kunkle, sentenced 1985?, Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 40)
    - Texas: Leo Little, sentenced 1999-03-05, 2002; 2004; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 41)
    - Texas: Michael Lopez, sentenced 1999 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 42)
    - Texas: Miguel Martinez, sentenced 1992-04-08, 1993; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 43)
    - Texas: John Matson, Jr., sentenced 1986-04-17, Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 44)
    - Texas: Laquan Miles, sentenced 1993, Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 45)
    - Texas: Jose' Ignacio Monterrubio, sentenced 1994-11-09, 2002; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 46)
    - Texas: Oscar Ortiz, sentenced 1995, Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 47)
    - Texas: Efrain Perez, sentenced 1994-09-22, 1996; 2004; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 48)
    - Texas: Whitney Reeves, sentenced 2000, 2002 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 49)
    - Texas: Johnny Rey, sentenced 1992-02, Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 50)
    - Texas: Magdaleno Rodriguez, sentenced 1981-06-29, Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 51)